She looks like a sheep.
Toilet.
That much?
But it's good, right?
It's so good!
We are now at Roseanne Billy Tawata!
Since we are in Shiga Prefecture, we wanted to be in a sightseeing spot, so we came to Roseanne Billy Tawata.
So I came to Roseanne Billy Tawata's. Here I am. I'm in Shiga Prefecture.
The weather is really nice today.
It's a beautiful day. It's super sunny, so I'm going to do some sightseeing while looking for a tea bucket.
So, shall we go?
I'm going.
It's hot, isn't it?
It's hot here in May, but it's always hot in May.
It's hot here, isn't it? There are a lot of nice cafes here.
Sure, so if we're going to go to all this trouble, we might as well eat something, right?
I want some. I'm probably pretty hungry.
I'm pretty hungry too.
Here's the entrance.
Flowers are beautiful. Flowers are beautiful.
I love flowers.
It's so bright.
You'll need a parasol today.
Because it's a high of 28 degrees or 9 degrees.
It's summer!
Oh, wait, Fridaire Square!
I want to go to the farm!
I want to go to the farm.
Thank you very much.
Let's go!
Like a sheep.
There's a shortage of animals these days.
It's so beautiful.
Amazing.
The air is so clean. It's kind of nice. Gentle. No, I know what you mean. You like the Tsumire countryside. I love it. I love it.
That's why it's perfect for me. Yes, I'm so happy.
It makes me want to go there. I want to go to Valencia. I really want to go to Barangay. That's why I'm happy now. It's so beautiful here. It's kind of Instagram-worthy, isn't it?
It's very Insta-worthy.
It smells good. It smells really good.
It's beautiful. Doesn't it smell really good?
How about using this as a background? Oh, that's a good idea.
Here. Oh, not so much?
But it's good, right? It's nice. It's so beautiful.
Beautiful. It's hot.
It's hot. The sunlight. It's really hot.
There's something here. It's true.
The face of a fan at the sheep show. I think I'll show it over there.
Sure thing.
Here it is. This way.
Fairy Garden Sheep Show.
There's a farm. Oh, that's the one I want to go to. Touch and feel. I want to go to the exciting farm. Let's go there. If we go to the exciting farm, absolutely. Yes, but I want to eat something.
But I want to eat something. Honestly. Yes, I want to eat something. Yes, I want to eat something. I'm looking for a receptacle for tea, so this time. That's right.
Don't you think they already have some? There was some bread or something. This place has a kind of Western atmosphere.
Isn't it nice?
You can experience it.
Korean fair.
Making key chains for the sheep show.
I want to make one!
They're so cute!
I want to go to a sheep show!
Isn't that what they do?
Aren't you supposed to feed them or something?
I want to feed them!
They're going up the hill now.
Wait, this is bad.
Oh, no!
I went to Miyagi and saw the waterfall.
We really climbed a mountain already!
Isn't it crazy?
You climbed a mountain?
Yes, we climbed a mountain.
We climbed a mountain.
What? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Some of them look like Roban.
Can you touch them?
Wait, there's a profile.
I'll take a picture.
Wait, aren't you scared?
I'm scared.
Yes, I'm afraid of it.
This is the baby. Chubby.
I like Chubby.
Yeah, I want to see Chubby.
You want to find Chubby?
Yeah, let's find Chubby.
This is what you wipe with, right?
I see what you mean.
It's a disinfectant mat.
Oh, no.
MEG.
Oh, it's cute.
Cute.
Not a baby. Chubby.
I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you.
It's adorable.
Oh, I'm sure it is.
Is he sleeping?
What are you doing?
That's a baby drawing.
It's cute.
And there's a sheep in the back.
Wow, he's so cute.
Great horns!
Chubby?
It doesn't say "boofir" on it.
But they say it was a chubby.
Look at him, he's so cute... he looks like he's lying down.
Is it hot in here?
I'm so scared.
Bye-bye, Javi!
Touch it.
It's got a big horn.
Oh, man.
How long does it take to grow?
This horn is amazing!
Oh, my God.
He's so smart.
It's over here, but...
His ears are moving.
His head is so big.
His head is awesome.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
Bye, bye, bye, bye.
Bye-bye.
Me too, daughter.
Daughter.
A little tiny.
I think she's tiny
Cute.
That's really hard.
Moo goo goo
Nice.
Cute.
Mushimushimusu
mmmm
So cute.
What are you eating?
Come here.
What's wrong with you?
Hello!
Are you seeing this?
You're doing a lot of eye work, there.
I don't have anything in my mouth like I did the other day.
Dick!
Cute.
Not cute.
Bye-bye.
He's so cute.
Well, that was soothing.
Wait, I want to show my true colors.
Right, Natsumi Nakayama, one time.
I've learned how to ride a horse.
But you can't ride a pony?
Ponies are miniature.
I've got everything.
Let's go in the back.
Pony.
Oh, they're so cute.
So cute!
Kota and Koharu.
Hey, they're cute!
Kota, Kota, Koharu, good luck!
I want to give you a carrot.
I want to give you carrots. I really want to give you carrots.
Oh, no.
Kota and Koharu.
Oh, wow.
Here they come!
I wonder if they're playing cute with each other... because I'm thinking of going back.
I wanted to go to the shade!
I saw ponies, sheep, and lambs... and I heard they wanted to eat something... and I heard they ate something... and they ate something...
I got hungry...
It's hot!
The sun was shining so brightly.
Mountains everywhere you look.
There's definitely a lot of greenery!
Mountains at 3,600 meters.
But I live in a place like this.
That's right.
Kaga City.
I want to go to Kaga too.
Really?
You haven't been there yet. On a tea ceremony.
Not on a tea ceremony.
What?
We're not on camera.
Don't you want to see us, camera girl?
Isn't she pretty?
It's got ribbons on it.
White.
He likes me.
There it is.
I'm wearing this.
Tutu dren.
Oh, no!
It's all wrapped up in a lion's head.
Oh, my God!
The ending is coming out!
Bike Bike Bike
Motorcycle Motorcycle
LOL!
Fell off.
that's awesome!
Someone will get the message.
Wow, I want some good food.
You couldn't have said it better yourself.
I mean, really, but you're pretty misquoted.
Really.
I'd like to try the barley beef croquettes now.
Dotchi's Goromi beef
Yes, I'll have the barley, croquettes and tea
Bon appétit!
Because this and soft serve ice cream
Yes, it's a privilege child
Bon appétit!
This one, this one?
Yes, this way.
Bon appétit!
It's so good!
This one's crispy, too.
It's really good!
I ate the croquettes too delicious.
I'm impressed. I can feel the barley.
What is this inside? Ingredients?
Yeah, it's so rich.
You know what I mean?
It's moist.
Yeah, it is.
It's delicious.
You have to try it.
Oh, it's so good.
It's delicious.
It's so hot today.
Even if you eat something hot, it tastes so good.
Yeah.
And I'm going to try the soft-serve ice cream.
Oh no, it's pretty much melted.
Bon appétit!
I'll try some too!
It's so good!
It's really rich!
What?
What? Oh, my God.
What is it?
It's...
I don't know how to say it. It's like 100%. It's like 100%.
It's really good. It's really good.
It's great in the summer.
It's so good!
The batter is really crispy!
I haven't had croquettes in a really long time, but they're so good!
I'm a huge pork cutlet fan... but it's really good!
It's just as good as katsu.
You like it now? Yes, I do.
You like it this way? Maybe I'm more this way. It's great! And it's got a lot of meat in it.
I really love it. I love food. I love it.
I love you, I love you, I love you, it's delicious, it's delicious, thank you for the food, thank you for the food.
I'll make it easier to eat the ice cream.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you for watching!